VALERI GETSOV

Angular Developer

- @ valeri@getsov.dev
- https://getsov.dev/

- www.linkedin.com/in/vgetsov
- Ruse, Bulgaria (Europe)



EXPERIENCE

Team Lead, Full Stack Development (MEAN stack + Ionic)

Race Fanatic

10/2023 - Present Present Remote

All in one Motorsport Events hybrid mobile app - https://racefanatic.app

- Led a dynamic team in the development of a pioneering hybrid mobile application for motorsport events, showcasing leadership in navigating project challenges and driving the project to completion.
- Orchestrated collaboration between 3 frontend developers, 2 backend developers, and a UI/UX designer, fostering a cohesive and innovative working environment.
- Spearheaded the application's frontend development using lonic and Angular, ensuring a seamless and engaging user experience.
- Guided the backend team in creating robust server-side solutions with NodeJS, ExpressJS, and MongoDB, enhancing application performance and security.
- Oversaw the design and implementation of an admin panel using Angular 17, featuring standalone components and signals, demonstrating cutting-edge project management and technical
- Championed a culture of continuous learning and professional growth, mentoring junior developers and a designer in adopting best practices and advancing their skills.

Hybrid Mobile Application Developer (Ionic + Angular)

Essence Group

Product Company

- Developing a hybrid mobile application from scratch, using the latest versions of Angular and Ionic (with both Cordova and Capacitor) for cosmetic niche needs.
- Utilized Angular Schematics for generating custom files from the CLI
- Helped the team with Swagger UI and NestJS

Full Stack Developer

Motion Software

= 08/2021 - 03/2022 Remote

Outsourcing Company

Has been promoted to Full Stack MEAN Developer to maintain and add new features for the website of the same coaching company, adding ExpressJS, MongoDB and NodeJS to the Front End stack, which lead to about 50% increased coaching sessions sales

Front End Developer

Motion Software

= 05/2021 - 08/2021 Remote

Outsourcing Company

Maintaining and building new features for a leading coaching company, using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Angular, WordPress, PHP (for the WordPress needs), which lead to better UX and performance

SUMMARY

Front End Developer with 6+ years of experience in building websites and hybrid mobile apps with great usability, less bounce rate, but higher conversion rate, using clean, reusable and well commented code. Proficient with the tools and the technologies mentioned below in the Skills section. Focused on how to improve my work and doing it the best way I can, while continuously looking for new ways to grow and expand my skill set. Worked with big companies in Bulgaria, Austria, Israel and the United Kingdom, which lead to faster understanding and implementing the business goal, the main point and the details.

SKILLS

HTML5	CSS3	Java	JavaScript		
jQuery	Angular	Ionic			
TypeScri	ript Cordova		Capacitor		
NodeJS	ExpressJS		MongoDB		
WordPres	s Oper	nCart	SEC	0	
GitHub	BitBucke	et <i>i</i>	Agile	Jira	

FIND ME ONLINE



GitHub

https://github.com/Getsov



Stack Overflow

https://stackoverflow.com/users/870365 9/getsov



LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vgetsov/



Twitter

https://twitter.com/ValeriGetsov

EXPERIENCE

Angular/Ionic Developer

Bulpont Ltd

m 01/2019 - 12/2020 Remote

Software company

- · When my Angular training was certified, I was promoted to build and maintain a couple hybrid applications, using mainly lonic and Angular
- Used Ionic Pro (now named Appflow) for live deploying without the need to update the versions in the Play Store
- Was constantly improving my Ionic skills through Simon Grimm paid membership at ionicacademy.com
- Developed 5 apps (4 of which still live in Google Play), used by hundred of users

Front End Developer

Bulpont Ltd

= 05/2017 - 01/2019 Remote

Software company

· Building and maintaining custom websites mainly for big Austrian companies, using mainly HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery

Junior SEO Specialist

Netpeak

Digital Marketing Agency

- · Creating manual SEO Audits
- Inspecting On-page optimizations on clients websites and giving proposals for improvements
- Keywords selections
- Was promoted to Head of Off-page optimization
- All of that lead to increasing the organic search positions and client's

TRAININGS

Certificate of Attendace Angular Global Summit 23 Vol.2

Certificate of Attendace JS Poland Conference 2022

NG Poland Conf

Certificate of Attendance NG Poland Conference 2022

NG Poland Conf

Upskill SalesForce Commerce Cloud

Telerik Academy, Remote

Accelerated ES6 JavaScript Training

Udemy, Remote

Agile Software Development

SoftUni, Bulgaria

Soft Skills for IT Professionals

SoftUni, Bulgaria

EDUCATION

Unofficial Team Lead Academy

SoftUni, Bulgaria

苗 10/2023 - 02/2024

Upskill SalesForce Commerce

Telerik Academy, Remote

= 10/2021 - 03/2022

JavaScript Developer

SoftUni, Bulgaria

10/2016 - Present

Digital Marketing

SoftUni, Bulgaria

11/2016 - 08/2017

Master Degree Tourism and Travel Services Management

Tsenov Academy of Economics

= 09/2009 - 05/2014

LANGUAGES

Bulgarian

Native



English

Proficient



Spanish

Intermediate



TRAININGS

Ionic - Build iOS, Android & Web Apps with Ionic & Angular Udemy, Remote Angular Fundamentals SoftUni, Bulgaria ExpressJS Fundamentals SoftUni, Bulgaria JS Applications SoftUni, Bulgaria JS Advanced SoftUni, Bulgaria WordPress Basics SoftUni, Bulgaria

Web Fundamentals

Programming Fundamentals - Extended

SoftUni, Bulgaria

SoftUni, Bulgaria